export const jsQuizz = {
    questions: [
        {
            question:
                "Which of the following is a supervised learning algorithm?",
            choices: [
                "K-means clustering",
                "Random Forest",
                "K-nearest neighbors",
                "Principal Component Analysis",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Random Forest",
        },
        {
            question: "What is the purpose of the term 'overfitting' in machine learning?",
            choices: [
                "Fitting the model too well to the training data",
                "Underutilizing available features",
                "Adding noise to the data",
                "Choosing a small learning rate",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Fitting the model too well to the training data",
        },
        {
            question:
                "Which optimization algorithm is commonly used to update weights in a neural network?",
            choices: ["Gradient Descent", "Newton's Method", "Stochastic Gradient Descent", "Random Search"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Stochastic Gradient Descent",
        },
        {
            question: "What is the purpose of the 'ReLU' activation function in neural networks?",
            choices: [
                "To squash output values between 0 and 1",
                "To introduce non-linearity",
                "To perform regression",
                "To handle imbalanced data",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "To introduce non-linearity",
        },
        {
            question: "What is the role of a confusion matrix in machine learning?",
            choices: ["To visualize data distributions", "To evaluate classification model performance", "To reduce model complexity", "To preprocess textual data"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "To evaluate classification model performance",
        },
        {
            question:
                "Which machine learning task involves predicting a continuous output?",
            choices: ["Classification", "Clustering", "Regression", "Dimensionality Reduction"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Regression",
        },
        {
            question: "What is the main purpose of the 'test set' in machine learning?",
            choices: [
                "To train the model",
                "To evaluate the model's performance on unseen data",
                "To fine-tune hyperparameters",
                "To visualize data distributions",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "To evaluate the model's performance on unseen data",
        },
        {
            question: "Which of the following is an ensemble learning technique?",
            choices: [
                "Support Vector Machines",
                "K-means clustering",
                "Bagging",
                "Principal Component Analysis",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Bagging",
        },
        {
            question: "What is the purpose of regularization in machine learning?",
            choices: [
                "To increase model complexity",
                "To reduce model complexity and prevent overfitting",
                "To introduce non-linearity",
                "To preprocess raw data",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "To reduce model complexity and prevent overfitting",
        },
        {
            question:
                "Which metric is commonly used to evaluate a binary classification model?",
            choices: ["Mean Squared Error", "Accuracy", "F1 Score", "Root Mean Squared Error"],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "F1 Score",
        },
    ]
};